deliverydudes.com 2017-04-22

# Privacy - Delivery Dudes - Your Privacy is Important

Your Privacy is Important

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

Delivery Dudes, LLC. (hereafter referred to as Delivery Dudes) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

What this Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers Delivery Dude's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Delivery Dudes through a website owned and operated by Delivery Dudes.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Delivery Dude does not own or control, or of persons that Delivery Dude does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Delivery Dude websites link.

Collection of Personal Information

Any information gathered by Delivery Dudes is used to customize the Delivery Dudes experience, and is not shared or sold to any third parties, except as expressly provided for in this Privacy Policy.

You can visit the websites of Delivery Dudes without revealing any personal information. However, Delivery Dudes needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, receive Delivery Dudes newsletter, or use certain Delivery Dudes services.

When visiting Delivery Dudes, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Links to third party Websites We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Delivery Dudes Commitment to Data Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your Delivery Dudes Information is protected for your privacy and security.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We believe in protecting your information just as we would want our information protected.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Delivery Dudes will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

Electronic Communications

When you use any Delivery Dudes Service, or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail, texting or by posting notices on this site or through the other Delivery Dudes Services. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

Child Protection

We do not offer services to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will purge any information we receive from people we believe to be children under 13 from our database and cancel the corresponding accounts.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

Delivery Dudes may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of Delivery Dudes websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

Your Consent

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Delivery Dudes. If you have provided personal information to Delivery Dudes and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify delivery dudes [here](mailto:Legal@deliverydudes.com).

Questions or Suggestions

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies,   
please e-mail our [legal department](mailto:Legal@deliverydudes.com).

Email Address (If you want to be contacted)

Please select your location: 

Email Address (If you want to be contacted)

Please select your location: 

Please select your location: 

(Price is subject to change based on Market Price.)
